

ANDRÉS FELIPE BURBANO

Frontend developer

Contact

(57) 300-611-2631

andresburbano2105@gmail.com

Calle 23A Norte #3N - 75 Santiago de Cali, Colombia.

Links



https://github.com/Pipe12



https://pipe12.github.io/portafolio/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/afbs/

Languages

Spanish: native language

English: B2

Soft skills

Customer service Teamwork
Problem solving Flexibility
Innovative Organized

My 10+ years of experience in medical equipment management has allowed me to be passionate about programming, with experience in web development and implementation of technological solutions. My objective is to apply my skills as a front-end developer within a project management team. I bring my professional background to evaluate a project as a full entity to successfully design, program and implement solutions for clients.

Skills

| HTML | React JS | Ruby |
|------|------------|---------------|
| SASS | javaScript | Ruby on Rails |
| CSS | Git | |

Work experience

Freelance / independent consultant | August 2017 to present Consultant for the biomedical sector, offered the following services:

- Web development
- Technical support
- Developed and implemented preventive maintenance plan

Maintenance coordinator | December 2011 to July 2017 Mainco Health care S.A.S.

- Developed and succesfully implemented preventive maintenance plan.
- Delegated tasks to the team
- Ensured quality control standards
- Provided technical support for the operators

Co-founder | November 2008 to November 2011 Ciento 1 Biomedica

Provided technical support to electromedical equipment for hardware and software including customers service support.

Education

Platzi Master Program cohort 6 | August 2020 to Present

Platzi Master is an exclusive program for the top (0.1%) students of Platzi in web develoment.

https://platzi.com/blog/que-es-platzi-master (online)

Bootcamp web developer | January 2016 to March 2016

https://www.makeitreal.camp (online)

Post-graduate certificate in TPM (120 hours) | 2015 Universidad Autonoma de Occidente - Cali - Colombia.

Electromedicine specialization | January 2009 to January 2010 Universidad Autonoma de Occidente - Cali - Colombia.

Mechatronic engineer | September 1999 to September 2006 Unigversidad Autonoma de Occidente - Cali - Colombia.

Projects

Tech challenge 2nd edition | 2006 Award for best design. Cali, Colombia.

National robotics contest IEEE | 2005 3rd place. Bogota, Colombia.